froobi.com 2013-03-12

# Terms & Conditions

**ORDER ACCEPTANCE POLICY**

Your receipt of an electronic or other form of order confirmation does not signify our acceptance of your order, nor does it constitute confirmation of our offer to sell. Froobi.com reserves the right at any time after receipt of your order to accept or decline your order for any reason. Froobi.com reserves the right at any time after receipt of your order, without prior notice to you, to supply less than the quantity you ordered of any item. All orders placed over $500.00 ( USD ) must obtain pre-approval with an acceptable method of payment, as established by our credit and fraud avoidance department. We may require additional verifications or information before accepting any order. Froobi.com is a reseller to end user customers and does not accept orders from computer dealers, exporters, wholesalers, or other customers who intend to resell the products offered by Froobi.com.

**PROCESSING TIME**

If the item(s) on your order are in-stock, we will ship them as soon as possible from our warehouse or from one of our Distribution Warehouses located throughout the United States. If the item(s) on your order are out of stock, they will not be shipped until we have received and processed the backordered inventory in our warehouse.

**LISTINGS AND OFFERS**  
Listings on this website are not an offer to sell goods, rather, they are advertisements to receive offers. Any offer/order for more than 3 units per address, customer or company may be rejected, and all orders are subject to review and acceptance by Froobi.com. As all prices are subject to change, your order may not be accepted or we may have to communicate price changes or availability issues to you after you place your order.

**RETURN POLICY AND LIMITED GUARANTEE AGAINST DEFECTS**

Unless the item you ordered is considered Dead On Arrival (DOA), Froobi.com does not accept returns. This policy is due to the fact that our items are only available for one day and are already priced far below the retail value. Most of the products you buy from us are backed by the manufacturer's warranty that will cover issues of the item being broken or defective. If the item you received is DOA then it will be covered by our 14 day limited warranty.

Froobi.com's 14 day limited warranty is a defective exchange policy that provides for either repair or replacement (at our sole discretion) of merchandise that has been confirmed as DOA by either the manufacturer or Froobi.com. The 14 day limited warranty does not cover damages caused by shipping, normal wear and tear, faulty packaging, or cosmetic issues.

If the product you received qualifies for the Froobi.com 14 day limited warranty, please contact us at our [Customer Support Page](http://temp.froobi.com/contact/) or by email at support@froobi.com. We will send you an RMA form which you will need to include when you send us back the item. Products returned for exchange must be in new condition, original packaging and include all disks, registration cards, packing materials and other accessories, and be postmarked within 14 days of the invoice date. We will provide a replacement item or refund, not including shipping and handling. Customer is responsible for all freight charges.

After 14 days the product manufacturer warranty is the only warranty in effect. Terms and conditions may vary by product or manufacturer. Froobi.com will assist customers whenever possible in gaining satisfaction with product manufacturers.

**COPYRIGHT/TRADEMARK INFORMATION**

Froobi.com is a trademark of Froobi, LLC. This entire website, copy, images, logos, indicia, text, content, and unique method of showcasing products is copyright Froobi, LLC. All trademarks appearing herein are acknowledged. Permission to use documents delivered from this World Wide Web site and/or server and related graphics is restricted. The name of Froobi or any of the above trademarks or logos may not be used in advertising or publicity pertaining to distribution of this information without specific, written prior permission. The information contained in this website is subject to change without notice. We are not responsible for typographical, technical, or descriptive errors of products herein.

**TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS**

In the event a product is listed at an incorrect price or with incorrect information due to typographical error or error in pricing or product information received from our suppliers, Froobi.com shall have the right to refuse or cancel any orders placed for product listed at the incorrect price. Froobi.com shall have the right to refuse or cancel any such orders whether or not the order has been confirmed and your credit card charged. If your credit card has already been charged for the purchase and your order is canceled, Froobi.com shall immediately issue a credit to your credit card account in the amount of the charge.

**WARRANTY LIMITATIONS**

There are no other express warranties or conditions respecting the equipment. Implied warranties, if any, are limited to the duration of the express warranty provided herein. Some states do not allow limitations on how long an implied warranty lasts so that the foregoing limitation may not apply to you.

**LIMITATION OF LIABILITY**

In no event shall Froobi.com or any of its subsidiaries or affiliates be liable for any indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages including but not limited to loss of use, loss of data, loss of business or profits. Some localities do not allow the exclusion or limitation of incidental or consequential damages, so the above limitation or exclusion may not apply to you.

**Privacy Policy**

We are aware of the trust and confidence you demonstrate when you visit our website and provide us with information. The Privacy Notice below is posted to demonstrate our adherence to the practices you'll find common to the best websites online. We promise that we will treat your information with the same honesty and sensitivity that we have displayed throughout our company's history.

We will never share your email address, phone number or credit card information with any unrelated 3rd party except as necessary to fulfill transactions that you initiate.

**Froobi.com Privacy Notice:**

By visiting the Froobi.com website you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

**Changes to this Privacy Notice, Conditions of Use and Notices:**

This Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use will change over time and the use of information which we gather now is subject to these Notices and Terms as modified. Please check this page periodically as you continue to use our site to see if any changes have been made. This privacy notice was most recently changed on November 17th, 2007. If you visit our Web site your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Legal Notices, including the application of the laws of the State of California.

**Children:**

Froobi.com does not sell products to persons under the age of 18. If you are under the age of 18, you are required seek the approval of your parent or guardian to purchase products from this site.

**Personal Information Collected By Froobi.com:**

Froobi.com uses information that we collect from our visitors to personalize and improve your visit at Froobi.com. We gather the following types of information:

**Information you give us:**

Froobi.com collects any information which you enter on our Web site. This information is normally provided when you search, buy, participate in a contest, sweepstakes or on-line survey, or when you communicate with any of our departments such as customer service, sales or technical services through our Web site, telephone, mail or fax. You also provide information when you establish an account with us. Examples of the type of information you may supply us with include your name, address, telephone number, credit card information, e-mail addresses, and financial information such as your Social Security number. In some instances, we ask you for other people’s names and email addresses for the sole purpose of fulfilling your specific request to email certain specific.

**Automatic Information collected by us:**

We (or agents on our behalf) collect anonymous information from visits to our sites through the use of “Web Beacons.” Web Beacons are simply web page elements which may employ cookie technology that enable us to record anonymous data about visits to or transactions made on our web site. This anonymous information is sometimes known as “clickstream data.” We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics to improve your online experience, or customer service. No personal data is collected through the use of Web Beacons on our sites. Through the use of cookies, we may also collect and analyze the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as your browser type and version; operating system and platform; purchase history; confirmation when you open e-mail that we send you; and the URLs which lead you to and around our Web site including the date and time. Your browser allows you to reject cookies and software is available from third parties which will allow you to visit our Web site without providing this information. You are welcomed at our Web site if you use this software but we will not be able to offer you our personalized services and we will be unable to accept any online orders from you.

**Orders:**

If you place an order we use a secure order form which requires you to provide contact, billing, and financial information. This information is transmitted to your credit card company to authorize your purchase. At certain times we may offer financing options with or without third party participation. If you use a financing option, information provided by you (such as your address, birth date, social security number, and credit card number) may be used to request a credit report from third parties or may be sent to a third party for processing. You will always be informed of this at the time you select any available financing option. All information obtained from you in the course of transacting orders is used for the purpose of fulfilling your order in a timely manner and for communicating the status of your order with you. Additionally, upon placing an order, you may begin receiving the Froobi.com email newsletter unless you opt-out by contacting us through our Contact Page.

**Email Newsletter Subscription:**

If you request an email newsletter subscription, we will send you an email confirming your request. This confirmation process allows you to unsubscribe if you changed your mind and decided not to join the list. Furthermore, the confirmation email will alert you if someone else had entered your email address into our email newsletter. In order to make our emails more relevant and useful to you, our servers may receive a confirmation when you open email from Froobi.com.

**Sharing of Information with third-parties:**

Independent Contractors: We may employ other companies or individuals to provide certain services to us such as analyzing customer lists and data, providing marketing assistance, or consulting services. These third parties will have access to the information needed to perform their functions but cannot use that information for any other purpose. Any 3rd parties who use our data will be fully bound by this privacy policy. In no event will the data being used by any unrelated third party include your email address.

**Orders:**

We will never share any telephone number(s), e-mail addresses, or credit card information which you have given us with any marketing partner(s) or any unrelated 3rd party. We may, however, share your name and postal mailing address with a few carefully selected marketing partners. You may opt-out of sharing this information at any time by contacting our customer service department from our Contact Page .

**Aggregate information:**

We provide aggregate information to some of our business partners. This information does not allow them to identify you individually in any way.

**Credit card companies and shippers:**

When you buy something from us we send your credit card information, name, billing address and the amount of your purchase to your credit card company to verify and authorize the purchase. Your name, telephone number and shipping information must be provided to third party shippers such as UPS, Federal Express and the United States Postal Service to deliver your purchase. There also may be instances in which we drop-ship orders directly to you from one of our manufacturers or suppliers. These drop-shippers are only given your name, postal address, and telephone number for the sole purpose of fulfilling your order.

**Third Party Transaction-Level Data:**

If you visit our site from a third-party site the third-party site may be able to access select information from your individual transaction information. In order to track and credit your transaction the third-party site may give you a unique code, cookie or graphic which will uniquely identify you. This will only happen if you link directly from a third party site to our Web site. Any transactions made at our Web site while such a code is active will be reported back to the third party site. We will only report non-personal information to these sites such as the date of the transaction, the product(s) purchased and the amount spent. We will not report any information to these third party sites that will allow them to personally identify you and will never share your email address with any 3rd party. The presence of a 3rd party navigation bar atop our site is an indication that the third party site may be able to see your activity on our site.

**Link to Third Party Site:**

Our Web site contains certain links to third party sites, such as our vendors. Froobi.com is not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content found on these sites. We suggest that you check the Privacy Notice of each site you visit.

**Information about Third Parties:**

Froobi.com maintains relationships with other websites that operate as its affiliates, however, Froobi.com has no control over their activities. Froobi.com will immediately cease doing business with any affiliate that abuses the terms of the affiliate agreement. This includes, but is not limited to: spam, trademark infringement, predatory means of attracting visitors, or unlawful activities. To report abuse by an affiliate, please contact us from our [Customer Support Page](http://froobi.com/contact/) or by email at support@froobi.com.

**Law Enforcement and Protection of Users:**

We will release personally identifiable information to third parties and organizations when we believe it is appropriate for us to do so to comply with the law. We will also do so to cooperate with law enforcement investigations, comply with court orders or subpoenas, protect the legal rights of us and our users, or when we believe it is needed for fraud protection and/ or credit risk reduction.

**Business Transfer:**

In the unlikely event that Froobi.com is sold, has its assets acquired or transferred, whether voluntarily or involuntarily, or merges or becomes affiliated with any other division, individual or entity, any customer information owned or under the control of Froobi.com may be one of the transferred assets.

**Security:**

We employ the latest 128-bit encryption technology in all areas of the site which require you to provide your personal or account information, including online ordering, order status, catalog request and most contest forms. Your name, your personal information and especially your credit card number are safely stored in our proprietary systems behind our firewall. Once you type your personal information, it is sent instantly, encrypted, directly to our order processing system which is on a server separate from our internet server. To make sure you have the latest security features on your browser, you may want to download the most recent version of your favorite browser, which should have full SSL support.

**Choice/Opt-Out:**

Our Web site gives you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us. If you no longer wish to receive communications from us you may opt-out by contacting us from our [Customer Support Page](http://froobi.com/contact/) or by email at support@froobi.com.

**SSL Data Encryption:**

Our Froobi.com website is registered with site identification authorities to enable your browser to confirm our security identity before any transmission is sent. With this technology, the identity of our site is automatically confirmed behind the scenes prior to the transmission of any customer information requested to complete an online order and ensures that your data reaches your intended target or your browser notifies you (prior to your sending any personal information) that the potential receiving site looks suspicious and should be avoided. Security Guarantee: If you are using a security-enabled browser (such as Microsoft Internet Explorer version 2.1 or greater, or Netscape Navigator version 2.0 or greater), the information you send us regarding your purchase is encrypted, making it extremely difficult to read even if it is wrongly intercepted. At Froobi.com, we utilize industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to allow for the encryption of: potentially sensitive information such as your name and address and other critically sensitive information like your credit card number. Standing behind our security technology, we also provide our Website Security Guarantee, further ensuring that you are protected every time you buy online with us. For more details, take a look at this guarantee.
